[
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"করা\"",
        "Answer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আসা\"",
        "Answer": "Go"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"যাওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Come"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পান করা\"",
        "Answer": "Drink"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"খাওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Eat"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পড়া\"",
        "Answer": "Read"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"খেলা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Play"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গান করা\"",
        "Answer": "Sing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"লেখা\"",
        "Answer": "Write"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Give"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সাহায্য করা\"",
        "Answer": "Help"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"রাখা\"",
        "Answer": "Keep"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চেনা / জানা\"",
        "Answer": "Know"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দৌড়ানো\"",
        "Answer": "Run"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পছন্দ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Choose"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কাজ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Work"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আঁকা\"",
        "Answer": "Draw"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"শোয়া / শয়ন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Lie"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বসা\"",
        "Answer": "Sit"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কথা বলা\"",
        "Answer": "Speak"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চালানো\"",
        "Answer": "Drive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চুরি করা\"",
        "Answer": "Steal"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বলা'\"",
        "Answer": "Tell"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কথা বলা\"",
        "Answer": "Talk"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বলা\"",
        "Answer": "Say"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ডিম পড়া\"",
        "Answer": "Lay"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পরিশোধ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Pay"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ঘুমানো\"",
        "Answer": "Sleep"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সাঁতার কাটা\"",
        "Answer": "Swim"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"রান্না করা\"",
        "Answer": "Cook"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"নেওয়া / গ্রহণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Take"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আনা\"",
        "Answer": "Bring"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কেনা / ক্রয় করা\"",
        "Answer": "Buy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ধরা\"",
        "Answer": "Catch"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"শিক্ষা দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Teach"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চিন্তা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Think"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"যুদ্ধ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Fight"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চেষ্টা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Try"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কান্না করা\"",
        "Answer": "Cry"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ভাঁজা\"",
        "Answer": "Fry"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"শুকানো\"",
        "Answer": "Dry"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ঝাড়ু দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Sweep"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মুছে ফেলা\"",
        "Answer": "Erase"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মুছা\"",
        "Answer": "Wipe"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"তৈরি করা\"",
        "Answer": "Make"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পছন্দ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Like"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ভালোবাসা\"",
        "Answer": "Love"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সাক্ষাৎ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Meet"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"খাওয়ানো\"",
        "Answer": "Feed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পরিচালনা করা / নেতৃত্ব দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Lead"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অনুভব করা\"",
        "Answer": "Feel"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"রক্তপাত হওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Bleed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দেখানো\"",
        "Answer": "Show"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বহন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Carry"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কবর দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Bury"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"তাড়াতাড়ি করা\"",
        "Answer": "Hurry"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আবেদন করা / প্রয়োগ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Apply"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সত্যতা যাচাই করা\"",
        "Answer": "Justify"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হাসা\"",
        "Answer": "Laugh"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হাঁটা\"",
        "Answer": "Walk"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ডাকা\"",
        "Answer": "Call"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কাটা\"",
        "Answer": "Cut"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পরিষ্কার করা\"",
        "Answer": "Clean"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মারা / প্রহার করা\"",
        "Answer": "Beat"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ক্ষমা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Forgive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পাওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Get"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দেখা\"",
        "Answer": "See"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মনযোগ দিয়ে দেখা\"",
        "Answer": "Watch"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ভুল করা\"",
        "Answer": "Mistake"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উচ্চারণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Pronounce"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বানান করা\"",
        "Answer": "Spell"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জয়লাভ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Win"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জিজ্ঞাসা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Ask"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বিশ্বাস করা\"",
        "Answer": "Believe"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গ্রহণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Receive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"নাচা\"",
        "Answer": "Dance"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মরা / মারা যাওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Die"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উপভোগ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Enjoy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সোনা\"",
        "Answer": "Hear"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হত্যা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Kill"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মনযোগ দিয়ে শোনা\"",
        "Answer": "Listen"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দেখা / তাকানো\"",
        "Answer": "Look"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হারানো\"",
        "Answer": "Lose"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বিক্রি করা\"",
        "Answer": "Sell"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অধ্যয়ন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Study"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বুঝা\"",
        "Answer": "Understand"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বুঝানো\"",
        "Answer": "Convince"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ফেটে যাওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Burst"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গ্রহণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Accept"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উপদেশ দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Advise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বিজ্ঞাপন দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Advertise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Become"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দোষারোপ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Blame"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গিবত করা\"",
        "Answer": "Backbite"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বিরক্ত করা\"",
        "Answer": "Disturb"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সংগ্রহ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Collect"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"নিয়ন্ত্রণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Control"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সমালোচনা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Criticise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বিবেচনা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Consider"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আলোচনা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Discuss"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"তালাক দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Divorce"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বিতর্ক করা\"",
        "Answer": "Debate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অনুশীলন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Exercise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চর্চা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Practise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আলিঙ্গন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Embrace"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গুরুত্বারোপ করা / জোর দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Emphasise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গোর করা\"",
        "Answer": "Force"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পালিয়ে যাওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Escape"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উড়া\"",
        "Answer": "Fly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"লালন পালন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Foster"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"যত্ন করা / পরোয়া করা\"",
        "Answer": "Care"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"শেষ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Finish"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উপহার দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Gift"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পথ দেখানো\"",
        "Answer": "Guide"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মঞ্জুর করা\"",
        "Answer": "Grant"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ক্ষতি করা\"",
        "Answer": "Harm"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ঘৃণা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Hate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ধরা / অনুষ্ঠিত হওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Hold"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জানানো\"",
        "Answer": "Inform"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অপমান করা\"",
        "Answer": "Insult"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দাওয়াত দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Invite"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অবজ্ঞা করা / উপেক্ষা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Ignore"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অবহেলা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Neglect"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"এড়িয়ে চলা\"",
        "Answer": "Avoid"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বৃদ্ধি করা\"",
        "Answer": "Increase"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অনুপ্রাণিত করা\"",
        "Answer": "Inspire"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"শনাক্ত করা\"",
        "Answer": "Identify"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চুলকানো\"",
        "Answer": "Itch"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"যোগদান করা\"",
        "Answer": "Join"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বিচার করা\"",
        "Answer": "Judge"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"লাথি মারা\"",
        "Answer": "Kick"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চুম্বন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Kiss"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ঠোকা মারা / দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Knock"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"নির্ভর করা\"",
        "Answer": "Depend"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দান করা\"",
        "Answer": "Donate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"প্রত্যাশা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Expect"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অনুসরণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Follow"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গল্প করা\"",
        "Answer": "Gossip"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"শাসন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Govern"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পাহাড়া দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Guard"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পশু চরানো\"",
        "Answer": "Graze"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আশা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Hope"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ইতস্তত করা / দ্বিধা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Hesitate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ভাড়া করা\"",
        "Answer": "Hire"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"লুকানো\"",
        "Answer": "Hide"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উন্নতি সাধন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Improve"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কল্পনা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Imagine"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ইঞ্জেকশন দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Inject"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"তদন্ত করা\"",
        "Answer": "Investigate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জড়িত করা\"",
        "Answer": "Involve"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ব্রাশ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Brush"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"শেখা / জ্ঞানার্জন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Learn"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বজায় রাখা\"",
        "Answer": "Maintain"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মুখস্ত করা\"",
        "Answer": "Memorise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অসদাচরণ\"",
        "Answer": "Misbehave"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ব্যবস্থা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Manage"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মিশ্রিত করা / মেশানো\"",
        "Answer": "Mix"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"প্রয়োজন\"",
        "Answer": "Need"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"লক্ষ্য করা\"",
        "Answer": "Notice"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is English of\"ডাকাত\"",
        "Answer": "Robber"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"খোলা\"",
        "Answer": "Open"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বন্ধ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Close"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"তালাবদ্ধ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Lock"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"তালা খোলা\"",
        "Answer": "Unlock"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পরিকল্পনা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Plan"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"প্রার্থনা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Pray"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"শাস্তি দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Punish"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ধাক্কা দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Push"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"টানা / টান দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Pull"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ব্যাথা করা / কষ্ট দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Pain"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ঝগড়া করা\"",
        "Answer": "Quarrel"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অপসারণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Remove"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আচরণ\"",
        "Answer": "Behave"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"যোগ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Add"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উত্তর দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Answer"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"নির্মাণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Build"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"রাজি / সম্মত হওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ফুটানো / সিদ্ধ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Boil"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জ্বালানো / পোড়ানো\"",
        "Answer": "Burn"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উপস্থিত হওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Attend"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হাত বুলিয়ে আদর করা\"",
        "Answer": "Fondle"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"অতিথিসেবা\"",
        "Answer": "Hospitable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সময়নিষ্ট\"",
        "Answer": "Punctual"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ঝগড়াটে\"",
        "Answer": "quarresome"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গ্রেপ্তার করা\"",
        "Answer": "Arrest"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ভিক্ষা করা / চাওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Beg"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বদলানো\"",
        "Answer": "Change"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উদযাপন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Celebrate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"স্বপ্ন\"",
        "Answer": "Dream"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চেনা / চিনতে পারা\"",
        "Answer": "Recognize"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"উপার্জন করা\"",
        "Answer": "Earn"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"স্মরণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Remember"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ভাতিজি\"",
        "Answer": "Niece"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ফুলের তোড়া\"",
        "Answer": "Bouquet"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ভাতিজা\"",
        "Answer": "Nephew"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মনে করিয়ে দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Remind"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ভুলে যাওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Forget"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"আদেশ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Order"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"নিষেধ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Forbid"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জরো করা/ জমা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Gather"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"মুখোমুখি\"",
        "Answer": "Face"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সম্পূর্ণ করা / পূর্ণ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Complete"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"পাঠানো\"",
        "Answer": "Send"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ব্যয় করা\"",
        "Answer": "Spend"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বাঁকা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Bend"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"সন্দেহ করা\"",
        "Answer": "Doubt"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"প্রতারণা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Cheat"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গণনা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Count"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দাবি করা\"",
        "Answer": "Demand"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জবাই করা\"",
        "Answer": "Slaughter"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"নাপিত\"",
        "Answer": "Barber"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জোড়া\"",
        "Answer": "Pair"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হিজড়া\"",
        "Answer": "Hermaphrodite"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ঝামেলা\"",
        "Answer": "Mess"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কষ্ট\"",
        "Answer": "Trouble"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কোল বালিশ\"",
        "Answer": "Bloster"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বালিশ\"",
        "Answer": "Pillow"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"গালি দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Chide"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"জুয়া খেলা\"",
        "Answer": "Gamble"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হুমকি\"",
        "Answer": "Threat"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দেরি করা\"",
        "Answer": "Delay"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"দালাল\"",
        "Answer": "Broker"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"কৃপণ\"",
        "Answer": "Miser"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"খাদক\"",
        "Answer": "Gowrmand"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"লজ্জা দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Abash"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ঘামা\"",
        "Answer": "Sweat"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"ছাদ\"",
        "Answer": "Roof"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"হুমকি দেওয়া\"",
        "Answer": "Threaten"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"চিল্লানো\"",
        "Answer": "Shout"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is english of \"বর্ণনা করা\"",
        "Answer": "Describe"
    }
]
